Do you think the coast is clear?
是不是 她们已走远?
No one to see, no one to hear
没人注视 没人听见
Me sing out my song?
享受这孤单?
I think we're all alone
能尽情去表演
I don't need my name in lights
我不求华丽的流彩
That's not where I set my sights
和那观众的青睐
No, oh-oh, no, not me
不 噢 不 做自己
I don't need a stage to sing
放歌不需要舞台
I like the quiet, I like the calm
我爱平静 我爱安恬
To turn it up, to sing along
调高音量 放声歌唱
I'm not just shy
擦量双眼
Look close, and you will see
看不一样的我
There's so much more to me
认识我另一面
I'm just fine rehearsing on my own
一个人 唱歌时最自在
My hairbrush is my microphone
梳毛刷是我手中的麦
Look out now, I'm in the zone
别眨眼 我灵感无限
Yeah!
耶!
Can you feel it?
我的世界?
I like the quiet, I like the calm
我爱平静 我爱安恬
To turn it up, to sing along
调高音量 放声歌唱
I'm not just shy
擦亮双眼
Look close, and you will see
看不一样的我
There's so much more to me
认识我另一面
I soft out in a crowd
平时我害羞胆小
I whisper, "am I being too loud?"
怕自己 说话声音太吵
But when I close that door
当我把门关好
The crowd, it just wants more and more and more
世界将为我沸腾和高潮
I like the quiet, I like the calm
我爱平静 我爱安恬
To turn it up, to sing along
调高音量 放声歌唱
I'm not just shy
擦亮双眼
Look close, and you will see
看不一样的我
There's so much more to me
认识我另一面
I like my friends, I like my pets
朋友相陪 宠物为伴
I like to rock, do pirouettes
我爱摇摆 踮脚转圈
I'm more than shy
擦亮双眼
I'm more than you can see
看不一样的我
There's so much more to me
认识我另一面